



Mohammad Shahin Shah

O Home: Bhuiyaan Manjeel, Sobahanbag, Sitakunda, 4310, Chattogram, Bangladesh

Email: mohammadshahinshah3@gmail.com Phone: (+880) 1568022438

Phone: (+880) 1521537475 **Phone:** (+880) 1846830882

Website: https://mohammadshahin.com/ WhatsApp Messenger: +8801521537475

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/mohammadshahinshah03/

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohammadshahinshah/

Gender: Male Date of birth: 3 Mar 2000 Nationality: Bangladeshi

ABOUT ME

I am pursuing a Bachelor's in Computer Science and Engineering from International Islamic University Chittagong. And I'm very interested in computer vision and deep learning. My thesis focuses on fire classification with (depth-wise) separable convolutions and how we could integrate Inception and attention mechanisms to improve accuracy. Being a Teaching Assistant also comes with mentoring students in and out of the lab. I deeply enjoy sharing my passion for technology with interested, yet curious students. Outside of academics, I help at my full-time job at Excite AI as a Graphic Designer where I design visually appealing content to present on social media and pack into products. My career goal lies in the direction of making a research-focused artificial intelligence and computer science career.

WORK EXPERIENCE

[3 May 2024 – Current]

Graphic designer

Excite Ai

City: Dhaka | **Country:** Bangladesh

Created engaging social media graphics that drove user engagement and increased online visibility

[5 May 2024 – 2 Aug 2024]

Senior Executive Graphic Designer

Requin BD

City: Khulna | **Country:** Bangladesh

Teamwork, Checking Designs, and instructing new INTERNS.

[25 Dec 2023 – 31 Mar 2024]

Junior Executive Graphic Designer

Requin BD

City: Khulna | Country: Bangladesh

Teamwork, Checking Designs, and instructing new INTERNS.

[1 Sep 2023 - 30 Dec 2023] **Graphic Design Intern**

Requin BD

City: Khulna | **Country:** Bangladesh

I created graphics and visual content for social media campaigns while learning to fit myself into the professional environment.

[2 Mar 2024 – Current]

Secretary

IEEE CS BDC Web & IT Committee

City: Dhaka | **Country:** Bangladesh

As Secretary of the IEEE CS BDC Web & IT Committee, I help facilitate and coordinate our team efforts, manage communications, and help lead digital projects that increase the committee's engagement and technical endeavors.

[5 Feb 2024 – Current] **Co-Ordinator, Graphic Team**

IEEE Computer Society Bangladesh Chapter Secretariat

City: Dhaka | Country: Bangladesh



I have demonstrated expertise in using Photoshop and Illustrator to create innovative graphics.

[1 Aug 2023 – 30 Aug 2024]

Head of Department Creative and Design

Hult Prize at International Islamic University Chittagong

City: Chattogram | Country: Bangladesh

- Promoted a culture of collaboration, continuous learning, and creativity.
- Guided creative direction in alignment with brand goals and ensured design projects met standards.

[19 Jul 2023 – 21 Sep 2024]

Lead Graphic Designer

IEEE Computer Society IIUC Student Branch Chapter

City: Chattogram | Country: Bangladesh

- Utilized extensive knowledge of Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator to create high-quality images.
- Generated digital image files for use in digital and traditional printing methods.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[1 Apr 2020 – 30 Dec 2024]

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering

 International Islamic University Chittagong
 https://www.iiuc.ac.bd/

 City: Chattogram
 Country: Bangladesh
 Level in EQF: EQF level 6

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Bengali

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

Microsoft Office

Microsoft Word | Microsoft Excel | Microsoft Powerpoint

Graphic Design

Adobe Illustrator | Adobe Photoshop | Canva

Video Editing & Motion Grahics

Adobe After Effects | Adobe Premier Pro

UX Design

Figma | Sketch

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Literature

Traveling

Writing

Teaching